<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>betcha can&#39;t stick it </title>
    <link>https://miguel.moll.ninja/</link>
    <description>Recent content on betcha can&#39;t stick it </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>youremail@domain.com (Miguel Moll)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>youremail@domain.com (Miguel Moll)</webMaster>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2016. All rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2016 22:23:23 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://miguel.moll.ninja/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Signing VirtualBox Kernel Drivers</title>
      <link>https://miguel.moll.ninja/post/sign-vbox-kdrv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2016 22:23:23 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Miguel Moll)</author>
      <guid>https://miguel.moll.ninja/post/sign-vbox-kdrv/</guid>
      <description>I recently came across an issue with VirtualBox and Fedora 23 that took me a good while to address. With Secure Boot enabled, the built kernel modules failed to load. Instead of disabling secure boot, I decided to tackle the problem head on. Hopefully this will be use for some, most likely my future self.
I tried installing VirtualBox via both the repos and website with no luck. And after various logs referring to dmesg with nothing of value, off to the interwebs I went.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Try!</title>
      <link>https://miguel.moll.ninja/post/first-try/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2016 19:37:53 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Miguel Moll)</author>
      <guid>https://miguel.moll.ninja/post/first-try/</guid>
      <description>Finally moved the site over to Hugo! Ghost was fun for a while, but it just didn&amp;rsquo;t make sense for me to run a server at all. Static site generator such as Hugo is a perfect fit.
Hopefully I just use it more!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nice hat to go with that Linux</title>
      <link>https://miguel.moll.ninja/post/nice-hat-to-go-with-that-linux/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2015 15:37:53 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Miguel Moll)</author>
      <guid>https://miguel.moll.ninja/post/nice-hat-to-go-with-that-linux/</guid>
      <description>If it wasn’t made clear with my last post, I really like Fedora. I also run CentOS on all of my servers while professionally I’ve mainly used Ubuntu Server. I gave Fedora Server a spin one day but I’m not sure how I feel about the frequent upgrades I’d have to manage. Big fan of RedHat overall. I admit the bias while currently reading The Open Organization.
What I believe grabs me most is the technology ecosystem that comes from the RedHat/Fedora world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FreeBSD confession</title>
      <link>https://miguel.moll.ninja/post/freebsd-confession/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2015 20:52:24 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Miguel Moll)</author>
      <guid>https://miguel.moll.ninja/post/freebsd-confession/</guid>
      <description>Ever since I learned about this whole Linux thing I couldn’t put it down. Learning new things left and right. From programming to operations, it seemed the knowledge wouldn’t stop coming. My first distro was RedHat Linux 7.0. I do not miss those days downloading an ISO file over dialup using a resume-capable download manager. But I believe because of that first RedHat experience is why I love Fedora till this day.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>